awn.com 2014-11-21

# AWN Privacy Policy | Animation World Network

#### Updated September 11, 2014

This is the official privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") and statement of AWN, Inc., AWN.com, VFXWorld.com, AWNtv.com, AIDB.com, AnimationBlogspot.com as well as the associated web pages, features and functions made available to you from these websites (collectively, "AWN") and is a part of the Terms of Service agreement we have with you regarding your use of AWN. The protection of your privacy is important to us.  AWN has established the following guidelines and procedures protecting the privacy of all our users. This Privacy Policy applies to all products, services and websites provided under the AWN name or any AWN subsidiaries (collectively, AWN’s “Services.”) It explains how AWN treats personal information that we collect and receive on the AWN website from our users and visitors. You should be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to websites that you visit before or after your visit to AWN, to other third party services featured on the AWN website, or to third party advertisers or affiliates (collectively, "Third Party Services").

#### What information does AWN collect and how do we use it?

Personal information is information about you that is not otherwise available to the public. This may include but is not limited to account registration information such as your desired username and password, e-mail address, country, age and gender. Personal information may also include information about your personal preferences, such as IP address (which cannot personally identify you), survey responses (from which you can always opt-out), user communication, server log records, session or cookie tracking data. We may use the information we obtain from you to display content we think may be of interest to you. AWN also aggregates user data that can help us tailor and enhance our user’s experience. We may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on our Web sites to be targeted, in aggregate, to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the user’s experience and the effectiveness of the ads.

When you visit AWN, we place cookies on your computer, as is standard practice on many websites.  These cookies allow us to retain your individual preferences, uniquely identify your browser and help us enhance your user experience. Most browsers are set to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some AWN features and services may not work properly if your cookies are disabled.

#### With whom do we share information?

AWN will not distribute, sell or rent any of the personal information about you to other people or nonaffiliated companies except to enable the provision of services or products you have requested or when we have your permission to do so. Your e-mail address may be used by us for communications related to the AWN services, including but not limited to, sending you notices about new features, products, or other information of interest to you. You can always opt out of receiving these notices.

Our advertisers and affiliates may be provided general information or data regarding member usage patterns or interests, or other general demographic information so that they can better serve your needs and preferences. However, such disclosure will not include individually identifiable information. The collection of usage and interest information allows us to continually evolve AWN services, products and features so we can better serve our user needs.

However, AWN may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on AWN; (2) enforce the AWN Terms of Service; (3) protect the rights, property or personal safety of AWN, its users or the public; or (4) respond to claims that any published materials violates the rights of third parties.

In the event that AWN is acquired by another company, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party.

AWN is owned and operated in the United States of America and our servers are located in the United States of America. Therefore, the collection of user data is governed, to the extent they exist, by United States federal and state privacy law.

#### How do I access and modify my registration information?

All of your registration information is located in your account Profile and Personal Options.  Your profile can be edited at any time, by logging in with your username and password. In addition, within all communications we send you, we will always provide you with instructions for opting out from additional communication.

#### How does AWN protect my information?

AWN has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Your personal account is protected by your password, which you select. AWN uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect our user data and restricts our employee’s access to such data, except to those whose primary job function it is to maintain this data. Please note that apart from the commercially reasonable efforts we employ, due to conditions beyond our control, we cannot guarantee 100% security of user personal data nor ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

#### What about access for children?

AWN takes children’s online safety very seriously. We do our best not to allow children under the age of 13 to obtain an account and we do not knowingly collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13.

In the event that we or our Affiliates unknowingly send an e-mail or other message to a child (a person under the age of 13 years) who has registered with AWN in violation of the AWN Terms of Service, the child or the child's parent or legal guardian always have the right to opt-out from receiving future e-mails or text messages using the opt-out mechanism contained in the e-mail or message, or to request termination of the child's registration and status as a registered user with AWN.

#### What if AWN makes changes to this Privacy Policy?

AWN periodically may update this Privacy Policy. At our sole discretion, we will attempt to notify our users via email of any updates to this Privacy Policy. However, we encourage you to periodically revisit the Privacy Policy link on the AWN homepage and on the footer of each website page to ensure that you are familiar with the current version. You are responsible for reviewing any revisions to this Privacy Policy and your continued use of the AWN website and services after any change to the policy constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy.

Whom do I contact with questions about the Privacy Policy?

If you have a question or concerns regarding AWN’s website or Privacy Policy, please write us at [info@AWN.com](mailto:info@awn.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy) or at our postal address:

##### Attention: AWN Privacy Officer  
AWN, Inc.13300 Victory Blvd. Suite 365  
Van Nuys, CA 91401
